Department of Philosophy fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Department of Philosophy fonds
1963 - 1989
F-15
2.57 m of textual records 21 sound recordings: 33 audio cassettes, 4 audio reels
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Department of Philosophy
The Department of Philosophy was established by the Board of Governors in 1965 as one of the original Departments in the Faculty of Arts. The Department was responsible, through its Head, for the promotion of research and the development and delivery of programs in the discipline of Philosophy. Throughout its existence, the Department has had as its focus Western thought with a predominant analytic orientation. In keeping with the interdisciplinary approach of the University, the Department has been involved with the Cognitive Science and Humanities programs. A M.A. program was added in January 1967. The Department also had an informal liaison with the Ph.D. program at U.B.C., which in 1993 was formalized in the creation of a joint program.
Like other SFU departments, the Department of Philosophy was organized into a Head (renamed Chair in 1972) and departmental committees. The Chair was the chief administrative officer responsible for oversight of the operational budget; faculty tenure, promotion and salary recommendations; teaching assignments; and representation of the Department to external bodies. While the Chair had overall responsibility to the Department and the Dean of Arts for the efficient operation of the Department, most decisions were made at the committee level with major issues being referred to departmental meetings for decision. The Departmental Assistant was responsible for much of the day-to-day administration of the Department, which included the management of the departmental budget, the scheduling of courses, the provision of liaison with administrative offices, and advising students.
The number and composition of departmental committees varied little over time. In 1969, there were seven standing committees: Curriculum Review; Departmental Tenure; Faculty Search and Screening; Graduate Studies; Library; Undergraduate Studies; and Visiting Speakers. In 1994, there were also seven committees, with the main change being the creation of a Discipline Committee, and the movement of responsibility for graduate and honours admissions to the Committee of the Whole. Ad hoc committees were also formed when needed, such as in the case of the search for a new Chair.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of the body.
The fonds of the Department of Philosophy consists of records created and received in the course of the administration of the department and the carrying out of its functions of providing instruction and promoting research. The activities documented include policy and procedures development; the planning, initiation and administration of curriculum and programs; departmental and faculty meetings; faculty salary, appointment, promotion and tenure deliberations; departmental reviews; and the publication of journals and reports. The types of documents include meeting agenda, annual reports, correspondence, course outlines and examinations, faculty files, memoranda, minutes of meetings, and reports.
The titles and arrangement of series were provided by the archivist.
Angelo, A. A.; Grant, Arvid J.; Kenner, L.; Bennett, J. F.; Resnick, Larry; Bradley, Ray D.; Tietz, John H.; Swartz, Norman; Jennings, Ray E.; Sound recordings; Textual records
The records were transferred in a number of accessions from the Department between the early 1980s and 1999.
All accessions have been processed as of June 2004. Further accruals are expected.
Consult the inventory of the Faculty of Arts fonds, F-2.
Some access restrictions apply in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the appropriate series level description and the archivist.
File and item lists are available.
- Administrative files, 1969 - 1974; F-15-1; 5 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to departmental operating procedures and includes Departmental Assistant's binder.
  - Operating procedures, 1969 - 1970; F-15-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
  - Operating procedures (constitution), 1970; F-15-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-17)
  - Departmental assistant's binder, vol. 1, 1970 - 1974; F-15-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 15-17)
  - Departmental assistant's binder, vol. 2, 1970 - 1974; F-15-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 15-17)
- Correspondence, 1965 - 1982; F-15-2; 58 cm of textual records 1 sound recording: 2 audio cassettes
  Series consists of correspondence received and sent by the department Chair. Records include memoranda, reports, chronological correspondence, Chair's correspondence, and subject files. Records also include two cassette tapes of Jack Webster's radio program regarding faculty hiring at SFU.
  Access to records in the subseries "Subject files" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Chronological correspondence, 1965 - 1978; F-15-2-1; 5 cm of textual records
    - Chronological correspondence, 1965 - 1973; F-15-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1976; F-15-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-15-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1977; F-15-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1978; F-15-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
  - Memoranda, 1967 - 1979; F-15-2-2; 9 cm of textual records
    - Chairman's correspondence, 1967 - 1970; F-15-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
    - Chairman's correspondence, 1971; F-15-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
    - Chairman's correspondence, 1971; F-15-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
    - Chairman's correspondence, 1972; F-15-2-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
    - Chairman's correspondence, 1973; F-15-2-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
    - Chairman's correspondence, 1974; F-15-2-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 15-1)
    - Chairman's correspondence, 1977 - 1979; F-15-2-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 15-2)
    - Chair's correspondence, 1967 - 1969; F-15-2-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 15-17)
  - Subject files, 1965 - 1982; F-15-2-3; 44 cm of textual records 1 sound recording: 2 audio cassettes
    - Faculty hiring issues: Jack Webster radio program, 22 March 1973; F-15-2-3-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-2786, Audio cassette OBJ-2787)
      Webster, Jack; Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item1, F-15-item2.
    - Annual reports, 1968 - 1970; F-15-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-2)
    - Budget, 1968 - 1970; F-15-2-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-2)
    - Budget commitment reports, 1965; F-15-2-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 15-2)
    - Budget commitment reports, 1966; F-15-2-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 15-2)
    - Budget commitment reports, 1967; F-15-2-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 15-2)
    - Budget commitment reports, 1968; F-15-2-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 15-2)
    - Budget commitment reports, 1969; F-15-2-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 15-2)
    - Budget commitment reports, 1970; F-15-2-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 15-2)
    - Budget commitment reports, 1971; F-15-2-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Budget commitments reports, 1972; F-15-2-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Calendar changes, 1971; F-15-2-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Curriculum, 1967 - 1969; F-15-2-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Douglas F. Wallace Memorial, 1972 - 1973; F-15-2-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Enrollment study, 1970; F-15-2-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Essay contest, 1979 - 1980; F-15-2-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Faculty Association, 1969; F-15-2-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Graduate students, 1968 - 1969; F-15-2-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - J. Harding's thesis, 1970; F-15-2-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Honors tutorial, 1970 - 1976; F-15-2-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Letters to Editor - Peak, 1966 - 1967; F-15-2-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - New course proposals, 1969; F-15-2-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Study for Ph.D. program in Philosophy, 1968; F-15-2-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Philosophy club, 1968 - 1973; F-15-2-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Sabbatical leave, 1975 - 1978; F-15-2-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 15-3)
    - Space allocation, 1968 - 1975; F-15-2-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Speaker's Bureau, 1970 - 1975; F-15-2-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Special topics courses, 1974 - 1975; F-15-2-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Staff - salaries, 1969 - 1970; F-15-2-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Student complaints, 1974 - 1976; F-15-2-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Student participation, 1967 - 1972; F-15-2-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Student Plenum Constitution, F-15-2-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Transfer credit, 1974 - 1976; F-15-2-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Transfer credit, 1977 - 1980; F-15-2-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Visiting speakers, 1966 - 1968; F-15-2-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Visiting speakers, 1969 - 1970; F-15-2-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Visiting speakers, 1971 - 1972; F-15-2-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Visiting speakers, 1973 - 1978; F-15-2-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Visiting speakers - proposed, 1971 - 1974; F-15-2-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 15-4)
    - Departmental budget, 1969 - 1970; F-15-2-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 15-17)
    - Faculty hiring issues, 1974 - 1975; F-15-2-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 15-17)
    - Philosophy enrollment statistics, 1976 - 1982; F-15-2-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 15-17)
    - SFU enrollment statistics, 1966 - 1972; F-15-2-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 15-17)
    - Philosophy course enrollment and other statistics, vol. 1, 1965 - 1976; F-15-2-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 15-17)
    - Philosophy course enrollment and other statistics, vol. 2, 1965 - 1976; F-15-2-3-0-44 (Archival box - standard 15-17)
- Faculty files, 1963 - 1980; F-15-3; 75 cm of textual records 2 sound recordings: 4 audio reels
  Series consists of case files related to the appointment of faculty members. It includes correspondence, curricula vitae, memoranda, reports, and cassette tapes.
  Access to records in this series is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Appointment files, 1963 - 1980; F-15-3-1; 45 cm of textual records 1 sound recording: 1 audio reel
    - Ian Hacking, 23 July 1974; F-15-3-1-0-0-1 (Audio reel OBJ-1053)
      Hacking, Ian; Sound recordings
      Restricted in whole
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item34.
    - Appointments, 1974; F-15-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-5)
    - Appointment of Head, 1966 - 1967; F-15-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-5)
    - Chairman search, 1963 - 1966; F-15-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 15-5)
    - Chairman search, 1967; F-15-3-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 15-5)
    - Chairman search, 1967; F-15-3-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 15-5)
    - Faculty - A, 1964 - 1967; F-15-3-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 15-5)
    - Faculty - A, 1967 - 1971; F-15-3-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 15-5)
    - Faculty - B, 1972 - 1979; F-15-3-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 15-5)
    - Faculty - B, 1967 - 1971; F-15-3-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 15-5)
    - Faculty - B, 1966 - 1970; F-15-3-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 15-5)
    - Faculty - B, 1967 - 1974; F-15-3-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - B, 1966 - 1972; F-15-3-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - C, 1972 - 1973; F-15-3-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - C, 1973 - 1974; F-15-3-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - D, 1967 - 1971; F-15-3-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - D, 1973; F-15-3-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - D, 1972 - 1974; F-15-3-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - D, 1969 - 1971; F-15-3-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - F, 1966 - 1977; F-15-3-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - F, 1965 - 1968; F-15-3-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - G, 1971 - 1977; F-15-3-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - G, 1964 - 1972; F-15-3-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - G, 1973 - 1975; F-15-3-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - H, 1972 - 1974; F-15-3-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 15-6)
    - Faculty - H, 1970 - 1974; F-15-3-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - H, 1970 - 1976; F-15-3-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - H, 1972 - 1974; F-15-3-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - J, 1967 - 1972; F-15-3-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - K, 1965 - 1972; F-15-3-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - O, 1968 - 1969; F-15-3-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - O, 1969; F-15-3-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - P, 1976 - 1977; F-15-3-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - R, 1973; F-15-3-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - S, 1973 - 1976; F-15-3-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - S, 1969 - 1970; F-15-3-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - S, 1972 - 1976; F-15-3-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - S, 1969 - 1971; F-15-3-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - S, 1972 - 1973; F-15-3-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - S, 1966 - 1973; F-15-3-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - S, 1972 - 1974; F-15-3-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 15-7)
    - Faculty - T, 1967 - 1978; F-15-3-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Faculty - T, 1964 - 1972; F-15-3-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Faculty - T, 1966 - 1977; F-15-3-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Faculty - W, 1968 - 1972; F-15-3-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Faculty - W, 1971 - 1980; F-15-3-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Faculty - W, 1966 - 1967; F-15-3-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Faculty - W, 1969 - 1975; F-15-3-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Faculty - Z, 1965 - 1968; F-15-3-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Faculty - Z, 1972 - 1974; F-15-3-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
  - Salary review files, 1971 - 1978; F-15-3-2; 6 cm of textual records
    Access to records in this series is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information
    - Salary review, 1971; F-15-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Salary review, 1972; F-15-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Salary review, 1973; F-15-3-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Salary review, 1974; F-15-3-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 15-8)
    - Salary review, 1975 - 1976; F-15-3-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Salary review, 1977 - 1978; F-15-3-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
  - Research grant files, 1969 - 1971; F-15-3-3; 1 cm of textual records
    - Awards and research grants, 1969 - 1971; F-15-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
  - Correspondence, 1967 - 1980; F-15-3-4; 22 cm of textual records 1 sound recording: 3 audio reels
    - Special lecture by Saul Kripke: The Metaphysics of Time and Identity, October 28–30, 1980; F-15-3-4-0-0-1 (Audio reel OBJ-1054, Audio reel OBJ-1055, Audio reel OBJ-1056)
      Kripke, Saul; Sound recordings
      Duration: 5
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item35, F-15-item36, F-15-item37.
    - Confidential correspondence, 1970 - 1971; F-15-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Personal - Angelo, Anthony A., 1968 - 1971; F-15-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Personal - Bradley, Raymond D., 1970 - 1973; F-15-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Personal - D'Alessio, Joan C., 1970 - 1971; F-15-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Personal - Davis, Steven, 1973; F-15-3-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Personal - Finn, David R., 1969 - 1974; F-15-3-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Personal - Grants, Arvid J., 1967 - 1972; F-15-3-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Personal - Herbst, Peter, 1970 - 1972; F-15-3-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Personal - Herbst, Peter, 1973 - 1980; F-15-3-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Personal - Jennings, Raymond E., 1967 - 1970; F-15-3-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Personal - Jennings, Raymond E., 1970 - 1972; F-15-3-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 15-9)
    - Personal - Kenner, Lionel, 1969 - 1973; F-15-3-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 15-10)
    - Personal - Swartz, Norman M., 1967 - 1970; F-15-3-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 15-10)
    - Personal - Swartz, Norman M., 1971 - 1977; F-15-3-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 15-10)
    - Personal - Tietz, John H., 1968 - 1973; F-15-3-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 15-10)
    - Personal - Todd, Donald D., 1968 - 1973; F-15-3-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 15-10)
    - Personal - Wallace, Douglas F., 1969 - 1972; F-15-3-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 15-10)
    - Personal - Wheatley, Jon, 1974 - 1980; F-15-3-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 15-10)
  - Curriculum vitae, 1971 - 1973; F-15-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-5)
- Departmental meeting and committee files, 1964 - 1978; F-15-4; 39 cm of textual records 18 sound recordings: 31 audio cassettes
  Series consists of the records of various departmental committees. It incudes circulars, correspondence, minutes of meetings, memoranda, and cassette tapes.
  Access to records in the subseries "Tenure committee" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult with the archivist for further information.
  - Department meeting files, 1966 - 1977; F-15-4-1; 12 cm of textual records 18 sound recordings: 31 audio cassettes
    - Plagarism discussion, April 1973; F-15-4-1-0-0-1 (Audio cassette OBJ-2797)
      Sound recordings
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item3.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 27 May 1975; F-15-4-1-0-0-2 (Audio cassette OBJ-2798, Audio cassette OBJ-2799)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item4, F-15-item5.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 16 September 1975; F-15-4-1-0-0-3 (Audio cassette OBJ-2800, Audio cassette OBJ-2801)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item6, F-15-item7.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 24 September 1975; F-15-4-1-0-0-4 (Audio cassette OBJ-2802)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item8.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 30 September 1975; F-15-4-1-0-0-5 (Audio cassette OBJ-2803)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item9.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 4 November 1975; F-15-4-1-0-0-6 (Audio cassette OBJ-2804, Audio cassette OBJ-2805)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item10, F-15-item11.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recordings, 18 November 1975; F-15-4-1-0-0-7 (Audio cassette OBJ-2806, Audio cassette OBJ-2807)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item12, F-15-item13.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 9 December 1975; F-15-4-1-0-0-8 (Audio cassette OBJ-2808, Audio cassette OBJ-2809)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item14, F-15-item15.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 15 December 1975; F-15-4-1-0-0-9 (Audio cassette OBJ-2810)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item16.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 13 January 1976; F-15-4-1-0-0-10 (Audio cassette OBJ-2811, Audio cassette OBJ-2812)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item17, F-15-item18.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 21 January 1976; F-15-4-1-0-0-11 (Audio cassette OBJ-2813, Audio cassette OBJ-2814)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item19, F-15-item20.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recordings, 11 February 1976; F-15-4-1-0-0-12 (Audio cassette OBJ-2815, Audio cassette OBJ-2816)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item21, F-15-item22.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 24 February 1976; F-15-4-1-0-0-13 (Audio cassette OBJ-2817, Audio cassette OBJ-2818)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item23, F-15-item24.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 11 March 1976; F-15-4-1-0-0-14 (Audio cassette OBJ-2819)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item25.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 8 April 1976; F-15-4-1-0-0-15 (Audio cassette OBJ-2820)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item26.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 5 September 1976; F-15-4-1-0-0-16 (Audio cassette OBJ-2821, Audio cassette OBJ-2822, Audio cassette OBJ-2823)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item27, F-15-item28, F-15-item29.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, 4 November 1976; F-15-4-1-0-0-17 (Audio cassette OBJ-2824)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item30.
    - Departmental meeting: audio recording, [December 1976?]; F-15-4-1-0-0-18 (Audio cassette OBJ-2825, Audio cassette OBJ-2826, Audio cassette OBJ-2827)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-15-item31, F-15-item32, F-15-item33.
    - Departmental meetings, 1967 - 1970; F-15-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - small 15-11)
    - Departmental meetings, vol. 1, 1966 - 1971; F-15-4-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 15-18)
    - Departmental meetings, vol. 2, 1966 - 1971; F-15-4-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 15-18)
    - Departmental meetings, vol. 3, 1966 - 1971; F-15-4-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 15-18)
    - Departmental meetings, 1972; F-15-4-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 15-18)
    - Departmental meetings, 1973 - 1974; F-15-4-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 15-18)
    - Departmental meetings, 1974 - 1977; F-15-4-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 15-18)
  - Graduate Studies Committee files, 1968 - 1970; F-15-4-2; 3 cm of textual records
    - Graduate studies committee, 1969 - 1970; F-15-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - small 15-11)
    - Correspondence, 1968 - 1970; F-15-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - small 15-11)
    - Policies, 1968 - 1970; F-15-4-2-0-3 (Archival box - small 15-11)
    - Thesis submission, 1968 - 1970; F-15-4-2-0-4 (Archival box - small 15-11)
  - Departmental Tenure Committee files, 1964 - 1978; F-15-4-3; 23 cm of textual records
    - Minutes, 1970 - 1974; F-15-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 15-12)
    - Tenure committee, 1968 - 1969; F-15-4-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 15-12)
    - Tenure committee, 1970 - 1971; F-15-4-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 15-12)